const question = [
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "Which player has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Pele", "Johan Cruyff"],
        "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "In which year was the first FIFA World Cup held?",
        "options": ["1930", "1950", "1966", "1982"],
        "answer": "1930"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "Who is known as the 'Hand of God' in football history?",
        "options": ["Diego Maradona", "Pele", "Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo"],
        "answer": "Diego Maradona"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "Which country won the first-ever recorded international football match?",
        "options": ["England", "Scotland", "Brazil", "Germany"],
        "answer": "Scotland"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the UEFA Champions League?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Raul", "Robert Lewandowski"],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which stadium hosted the 2014 FIFA World Cup Final?",
        "options": ["Maracana Stadium", "Wembley Stadium", "Allianz Arena", "Estadio Santiago Bernabeu"],
        "answer": "Maracana Stadium"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Who won the Ballon d'Or in 2020?",
        "options": ["Robert Lewandowski", "Lionel Messi","Cristiano Ronaldo", "Kevin De Bruyne"],
        "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which team has won the most FIFA World Cup titles?",
        "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Italy", "Argentina"],
        "answer": "Brazil"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Who is the youngest goalscorer in World Cup history?",
        "options": [ "Diego Maradona", "Kylian Mbappe","Pele", "Michael Owen"],
        "answer": "Pele"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which player is known as the 'Black Pearl'?",
        "options": ["Pele", "Eusebio", "George Best", "Johan Cruyff"],
        "answer": "Pele"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "Which team won the first Women's World Cup?",
        "options": ["Germany", "USA", "Brazil", "Norway"],
        "answer": "USA"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the Women's World Cup?",
        "options": ["Marta", "Birgit Prinz", "Abby Wambach", "Mia Hamm"],
        "answer": "Marta"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "Which club won the first edition of the UEFA Champions League?",
        "options": [ "AC Milan", "Barcelona", "Real Madrid","Bayern Munich"],
        "answer": "Real Madrid"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have won the FIFA World Cup, UEFA Champions League, and Ballon d'Or in the same year?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi",  "Zinedine Zidane", "Cristiano Ronaldo","Franz Beckenbauer"],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "Which player is nicknamed the 'Egyptian King'?",
        "options": [ "Sadio Mane", "Mohamed Salah","Roberto Firmino", "Virgil van Dijk"],
        "answer": "Mohamed Salah"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the English Premier League?",
        "options": [ "Wayne Rooney", "Thierry Henry", "Andy Cole","Alan Shearer",],
        "answer": "Alan Shearer"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "Which country hosted the 2018 FIFA World Cup?",
        "options": ["Germany", "Russia", "Brazil", "France"],
        "answer": "Russia"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in three World Cup finals?",
        "options": ["Pele", "Diego Maradona", "Zinedine Zidane", "Miroslav Klose"],
        "answer": "Pele"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "Which club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
        "options": ["Barcelona", "Real Madrid", "Bayern Munich", "AC Milan"],
        "answer": "Real Madrid"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "Who is the fastest player to score 100 goals for a single club in the English Premier League?",
        "options": ["Thierry Henry", "Harry Kane", "Sergio Aguero", "Alan Shearer"],
        "answer": "Alan Shearer"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 21,
        "question": "Which player has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
        "options": [ "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Michel Platini", "Johan Cruyff","Lionel Messi",],
        "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 22,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in every minute of a football match?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Thierry Henry", "Zlatan Ibrahimovic"],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 23,
        "question": "Which country won the first African Cup of Nations?",
        "options": ["Nigeria", "Egypt", "Ghana", "Cameroon"],
        "answer": "Egypt"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 24,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the Copa America?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Neymar", "Zico", "Pelé"],
        "answer": "Pelé"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 25,
        "question": "Which player scored the fastest hat-trick in Premier League history?",
        "options": [ "Sergio Aguero", "Robbie Fowler","Sadio Mane", "Michael Owen"],
        "answer": "Sadio Mane"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 26,
        "question": "Who is the only goalkeeper to have won the Ballon d'Or?",
        "options": ["Lev Yashin", "Dino Zoff", "Gianluigi Buffon", "Oliver Kahn"],
        "answer": "Lev Yashin"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 27,
        "question": "Which club has won the most domestic league titles in Europe?",
        "options": ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "Manchester United", "AC Milan"],
        "answer": "Real Madrid"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 28,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have won the Golden Boot in three different leagues?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi",  "Thierry Henry", "Cristiano Ronaldo","Luis Suarez"],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 29,
        "question": "Which country hosted the first-ever FIFA World Cup for women?",
        "options": ["China","USA",  "Sweden", "Germany"],
        "answer": "China"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 30,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have won the UEFA Champions League with three different clubs?",
        "options": [ "Clarence Seedorf", "Xavi Hernandez", "Andres Iniesta","Cristiano Ronaldo"],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 31,
        "question": "Which player holds the record for the most goals in a calendar year?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Neymar", "Zlatan Ibrahimovic"],
        "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 32,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in 10 consecutive UEFA Champions League matches?",
        "options": ["Lionel Messi",  "Raul","Cristiano Ronaldo", "Robert Lewandowski"],
        "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 33,
        "question": "Which country has won the most Olympic gold medals in football?",
        "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Italy", "Argentina"],
        "answer": "Brazil"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 34,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the AFC Asian Cup?",
        "options": ["Miroslav Klose","Ali Daei",  "Sunil Chhetri", "Tim Cahill"],
        "answer": "Ali Daei"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 35,
        "question": "Which player is known as the 'Baby-faced Assassin'?",
        "options": ["Ole Gunnar Solskjaer", "Wayne Rooney", "Robin van Persie", "Ruud van Nistelrooy"],
        "answer": "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 36,
        "question": "Who scored the famous 'Hand of God' goal in the 1986 World Cup?",
        "options": [ "Lionel Messi", "Pele", "Diego Maradona","Zinedine Zidane"],
        "answer": "Diego Maradona"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 37,
        "question": "Which country has won the most African Cup of Nations titles?",
        "options": [ "Nigeria", "Cameroon", "Egypt","Ghana"],
        "answer": "Egypt"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 38,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the Dutch Eredivisie?",
        "options": ["Ruud van Nistelrooy","Willem II", "Robin van Persie", "Johan Cruyff" ],
        "answer": "Willem II"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 39,
        "question": "Which player is known as the 'Non-flying Dutchman'?",
        "options": ["Johan Cruyff", "Ruud Gullit", "Marco van Basten", "Dennis Bergkamp"],
        "answer": "Dennis Bergkamp"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 40,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have won the FIFA World Cup both as a player and a manager?",
        "options": [ "Diego Maradona", "Franz Beckenbauer","Zinedine Zidane", "Pele"],
        "answer": "Franz Beckenbauer"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 41,
        "question": "Which club has won the most consecutive English Premier League titles?",
        "options": [ "Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Manchester United","Chelsea"],
        "answer": "Manchester United"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 42,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the MLS (Major League Soccer)?",
        "options": [ "Chris Wondolowski", "Landon Donovan", "Bradley Wright-Phillips", "Josef Martinez"],
        "answer": "Chris Wondolowski"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 43,
        "question": "Which player has won the most FIFA Club World Cup titles?",
        "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Dani Alves", "Sergio Ramos"],
        "answer": "Dani Alves"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 44,
        "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in six different World Cup tournaments?",
        "options": [ "Pele", "Miroslav Klose", "Diego Maradona", "Lionel Messi"],
        "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 45,
        "question": "Which country has won the most UEFA European Championship titles?",
        "options": [ "Spain","Germany", "France", "Italy"],
        "answer": "Germany"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 46,
        "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the South American Copa Libertadores?",
        "options": ["Pelé", "Diego Maradona", "Romário", "Daniel Bilos"],
        "answer": "Daniel Bilos"
        },
        
        {
        "id": 47,
        "question": "Which player has won the most UEFA Super Cup titles?",
        "options": ["Dani Alves", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Sergio Ramos"],
        "answer": "Dani Alves"
        },
        {
            "id": 48,
            "question": "Who scored the 'Goal of the Century' in the 1986 World Cup?",
            "options": [ "Gary Lineker", "Jorge Valdano", "Diego Maradona","Hugo Sanchez"],
            "answer": "Diego Maradona"
        },
        
        {
            "id": 49,
            "question": "Which English club has won the most top-flight league titles?",
            "options": [ "Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Chelsea", "Manchester United",],
            "answer": "Manchester United"
        },
        
        {
            "id": 50,
            "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in three different World Cup finals?",
            "options": [ "Diego Maradona","Pele", "Zinedine Zidane", "Cristiano Ronaldo"],
            "answer": "Pele"
        }













        // {
        //     "id": 11,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have won the FIFA World Cup as both a player and a manager?",
        //     "options": ["Diego Maradona", "Pele", "Franz Beckenbauer", "Zinedine Zidane"],
        //     "answer": "Franz Beckenbauer"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 12,
        //     "question": "Which country hosted the first Women's World Cup in 1991?",
        //     "options": ["United States", "China", "Sweden", "Germany"],
        //     "answer": "China"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 13,
        //     "question": "Who scored the fastest hat-trick in Premier League history?",
        //     "options": ["Sadio Mane", "Robbie Fowler", "Sergio Aguero", "Thierry Henry"],
        //     "answer": "Sadio Mane"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 14,
        //     "question": "In which year did the 'Bosman ruling' come into effect?",
        //     "options": ["1992", "1995", "2000", "2003"],
        //     "answer": "1995"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 15,
        //     "question": "Which club has won the most UEFA Champions League titles?",
        //     "options": ["Real Madrid", "Barcelona", "AC Milan", "Bayern Munich"],
        //     "answer": "Real Madrid"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 16,
        //     "question": "Who holds the record for the most goals in a single calendar year?",
        //     "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Neymar", "Zlatan Ibrahimovic"],
        //     "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 17,
        //     "question": "Which African country won the Africa Cup of Nations in 2019?",
        //     "options": ["Nigeria", "Cameroon", "Egypt", "Algeria"],
        //     "answer": "Algeria"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 18,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer of the English Premier League?",
        //     "options": ["Alan Shearer", "Thierry Henry", "Wayne Rooney", "Andy Cole"],
        //     "answer": "Alan Shearer"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 19,
        //     "question": "Which player has won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
        //     "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Pele", "Johan Cruyff"],
        //     "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 20,
        //     "question": "Who scored the 'Hand of God' goal in the 1986 World Cup?",
        //     "options": ["Diego Maradona", "Gary Lineker", "Jorge Valdano", "Hugo Sanchez"],
        //     "answer": "Diego Maradona"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 21,
        //     "question": "Which Italian club is known as 'The Old Lady'?",
        //     "options": ["AC Milan", "Inter Milan", "AS Roma", "Juventus"],
        //     "answer": "Juventus"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 22,
        //     "question": "Who is the top scorer in the history of the UEFA Champions League?",
        //     "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Raul", "Robert Lewandowski"],
        //     "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 23,
        //     "question": "Which country won the UEFA European Championship in 2016?",
        //     "options": ["Portugal", "France", "Germany", "Spain"],
        //     "answer": "Portugal"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 24,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the Brazilian national team?",
        //     "options": ["Pele", "Romario", "Ronaldo", "Neymar"],
        //     "answer": "Pele"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 25,
        //     "question": "In which city was the first FIFA World Cup held?",
        //     "options": ["Paris", "Berlin", "Montevideo", "Rome"],
        //     "answer": "Montevideo"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 26,
        //     "question": "Who scored the 'Goal of the Century' in the 1986 World Cup?",
        //     "options": ["Diego Maradona", "Gary Lineker", "Jorge Valdano", "Hugo Sanchez"],
        //     "answer": "Diego Maradona"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 27,
        //     "question": "Which English club has won the most top-flight league titles?",
        //     "options": ["Manchester United", "Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Chelsea"],
        //     "answer": "Manchester United"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 28,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in three different World Cup finals?",
        //     "options": ["Pele", "Diego Maradona", "Zinedine Zidane", "Cristiano Ronaldo"],
        //     "answer": "Pele"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 29,
        //     "question": "Which country has won the most Copa America titles?",
        //     "options": ["Argentina", "Brazil", "Uruguay", "Chile"],
        //     "answer": "Uruguay"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 30,
        //     "question": "Who is the youngest player to score in a World Cup final?",
        //     "options": ["Pele", "Diego Maradona", "Kylian Mbappe", "Michael Owen"],
        //     "answer": "Pele"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 31,
        //     "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 1954?",
        //     "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Italy", "Uruguay"],
        //     "answer": "West Germany"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 32,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer in the history of the FIFA World Cup?",
        //     "options": ["Miroslav Klose", "Pele", "Gerd Muller", "Ronaldo Nazario"],
        //     "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 33,
        //     "question": "In which year did the Premier League begin?",
        //     "options": ["1990", "1992", "1994", "1996"],
        //     "answer": "1992"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 34,
        //     "question": "Which player has won the most Premier League Golden Boot awards?",
        //     "options": ["Alan Shearer", "Thierry Henry", "Harry Kane", "Sergio Aguero"],
        //     "answer": "Alan Shearer"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 35,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have won the Ballon d'Or with three different clubs?",
        //     "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Michel Platini", "Johan Cruyff"],
        //     "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 36,
        //     "question": "Which country hosted the first-ever World Cup in 1930?",
        //     "options": ["Brazil", "Argentina", "Uruguay", "Italy"],
        //     "answer": "Uruguay"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 37,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the Spanish national team?",
        //     "options": ["David Villa", "Fernando Hierro", "Fernando Torres", "David Silva"],
        //     "answer": "David Villa"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 38,
        //     "question": "Which club won the first edition of the UEFA Champions League in 1956?",
        //     "options": ["Real Madrid", "AC Milan", "Barcelona", "Manchester United"],
        //     "answer": "Real Madrid"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 39,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in 11 consecutive Premier League matches?",
        //     "options": ["Thierry Henry", "Ruud van Nistelrooy", "Sergio Aguero", "Jamie Vardy"],
        //     "answer": "Jamie Vardy"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 40,
        //     "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 1978?",
        //     "options": ["Brazil", "Argentina", "Italy", "Germany"],
        //     "answer": "Argentina"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 41,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the French national team?",
        //     "options": ["Thierry Henry", "Michel Platini", "David Trezeguet", "Zinedine Zidane"],
        //     "answer": "Thierry Henry"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 42,
        //     "question": "Which player holds the record for the most appearances in the FIFA World Cup?",
        //     "options": ["Lothar Matthaus", "Cafu", "Miroslav Klose", "Diego Maradona"],
        //     "answer": "Lothar Matthaus"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 43,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the German national team?",
        //     "options": ["Miroslav Klose", "Gerd Muller", "Thomas Muller", "Jurgen Klinsmann"],
        //     "answer": "Miroslav Klose"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 44,
        //     "question": "Which English club is known as 'The Red Devils'?",
        //     "options": ["Liverpool", "Manchester United", "Arsenal", "Chelsea"],
        //     "answer": "Manchester United"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 45,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have scored in all six club competitions recognized by FIFA?",
        //     "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Neymar", "Andres Iniesta"],
        //     "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 46,
        //     "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 1966?",
        //     "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Italy", "England"],
        //     "answer": "England"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 47,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the Argentine national team?",
        //     "options": ["Diego Maradona", "Lionel Messi", "Gabriel Batistuta", "Hernan Crespo"],
        //     "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 48,
        //     "question": "Which club won the first edition of the FIFA Club World Cup in 2000?",
        //     "options": ["Real Madrid", "Manchester United", "Corinthians", "Bayern Munich"],
        //     "answer": "Corinthians"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 49,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have won the Golden Foot award twice?",
        //     "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Zlatan Ibrahimovic", "Andres Iniesta"],
        //     "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 50,
        //     "question": "Which country won the UEFA European Championship in 2008?",
        //     "options": ["Spain", "Germany", "Netherlands", "Italy"],
        //     "answer": "Spain"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 51,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the Portuguese national team?",
        //     "options": ["Eusebio", "Luis Figo", "Pauleta", "Cristiano Ronaldo"],
        //     "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 52,
        //     "question": "Which player has won the most FIFA Club World Cup Golden Ball awards?",
        //     "options": ["Lionel Messi", "Cristiano Ronaldo", "Zinedine Zidane", "Andres Iniesta"],
        //     "answer": "Lionel Messi"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 53,
        //     "question": "In which year did the Copa America tournament start?",
        //     "options": ["1916", "1924", "1930", "1940"],
        //     "answer": "1916"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 54,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the Dutch national team?",
        //     "options": ["Dennis Bergkamp", "Patrick Kluivert", "Robin van Persie", "Ruud van Nistelrooy"],
        //     "answer": "Robin van Persie"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 55,
        //     "question": "Which club has won the most FA Cup titles?",
        //     "options": ["Arsenal", "Manchester United", "Chelsea", "Liverpool"],
        //     "answer": "Arsenal"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 56,
        //     "question": "Who is the only player to have won the UEFA Champions League with three different clubs?",
        //     "options": ["Cristiano Ronaldo", "Lionel Messi", "Andres Iniesta", "Zinedine Zidane"],
        //     "answer": "Cristiano Ronaldo"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 57,
        //     "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 1934?",
        //     "options": ["Brazil", "Germany", "Italy", "Uruguay"],
        //     "answer": "Italy"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //     "id": 58,
        //     "question": "Who is the all-time top scorer for the Belgian national team?",
        //     "options": ["Romelu Lukaku", "Eden Hazard", "Jan Vertonghen", "Paul Van Himst"],
        //     "answer": "Romelu Lukaku"
        //     },
        //     {
        //         "id": 59,
        //         "question": "Who scored the 'Goal of the Century' in the 1986 World Cup?",
        //         "options": ["Diego Maradona", "Gary Lineker", "Jorge Valdano", "Hugo Sanchez"],
        //         "answer": "Diego Maradona"
        //     },
            
        //     {
        //         "id": 60,
        //         "question": "Which English club has won the most top-flight league titles?",
        //         "options": ["Manchester United", "Liverpool", "Arsenal", "Chelsea"],
        //         "answer": "Manchester United"
        //     }
]

export default question